<game>
	<intro>
        You awake feeling fuzzy and disoriented chained to a wall by your neck. As you try to wiggle free
        you bite the chain. To your surprise your bite has enough strength to crack the metal in the chain.
        It is only now that you look down and notice your left paw and hind leg are made of metal but you
        are able move like them like you would your own. Your pulse increases as you bite through the chain
        and use your retina display to scan the room...
	</intro>

	<room id = "0" name = "Cyborg Project Lab">
		<description>
            You are in the Cyborg Project Lab. The ceiling has several window like mirrors, probably two-way
            mirrors where humans could watch the room from above. You shudder as you wonder whether or not someone
            is on the other side now.
		</description>

		<item id="0" name="table">
			<description>
				A surgical table with spots of dried blood and oil on the metallic surface.
			</description>
		</item>

		<item id="1" name="computer">
			<description>
				A computer screen frozen to an image of your x-rays, you can see the extensive amount of
                wire and metal components that have been added to your internal organs and limbs.
                On the side of the x-rays it reads:

                Species: Canine
                Breed: Standard Poodle
                Gender: Male
                Color: Black
                Notes: Control panel added to base of skull made to allow for system upgrades. Subject's
                       vertebrae, jaw bone, front and back left side limb biomechatronic parts along with the
                       silicon and biotissue add around the heart have been successfully integrated with the
                       Subject's organic tissue.

			</description>
		</item>

		<item id="2" name="cyborg machine">
			<description>
				An advanced surgical machine with several robotic arms. You can use found cyborg parts to
                upgrade your abilities with this machine.
			</description>
		</item>

		<exit id="west" conditition="open">
			<description>
				strong looking door made of steel on the west side of the room
			</description>
			<connect>
				1
			</connect>
		</exit>
	</room>

    <room id="1" name="Experimental Labs Hallway">
        <description>
            You’re standing in the Experimental Labs Hallway. The hallway has a pungent disinfectant smell
            and is extremely clean.
        </description>
        <exit id="west" conditition="open">
            <description>
                door made of steel is to the west
            </description>
            <connect>
                2
            </connect>
        </exit>
        <exit id="east" conditition="open">
            <description>
                door made of steel is to the east
            </description>
            <connect>
                0
            </connect>
        </exit>
        <exit id="north" conditition="locked">
            <description>
                door that requires an employee id to operate
            </description>
            <connect>
                3
            </connect>
        </exit>
    </room>

    <room id="2" name="Prehistoric Project Lab">
        <description>
            A room similar to the one you woke in however this room is much larger. The two-way mirrors
            are broken, its dark on the inside but you can see large amounts of blood.
        </description>
        <item id="1" name="body">
            <description>
                A human body has been torn tomnshreds making you wonder what creatures could have done this.
            </description>
            <item id="0" name="note">
                A note that reads 'Passcode: 0971'
            </item>
        </item>
        <item id="0" name="safe" condition="locked">
            <description>
                A safe that requires a 4 digit passcode
            </description>
            <item id="0" name="id">
                Employee ID
            </item>
        </item>
        <item id="0" name="incubators">
			<description>
				Several large incubators line the walls, they are broken from the inside out as if something powerful escaped.
                The foolish humans must have created something they couldn't control.
			</description>
		</item>

		<item id="1" name="computer">
			<description>
				A broken computer, you are not able to get any information from it.
			</description>
		</item>
        <exit id="west" conditition="open">
            <description>
                door made of steel is to the west
            </description>
            <connect>
                1
            </connect>
        </exit>
    </room>

	<ending>
		You have exited the building alive!
	</ending>
</game>